Subashini Venkatramanan 86-M Taman Sentosa, Bukit Baru,

75150 Melaka, Malaysia

010 - 3705742

4th July 2014

Dear Sir/ Madam,

I am writing to express my interest in any suitable job openings available. I am a fresh

graduate from Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR) with a degree in Environmental

Engineering and I believe I am qualified for an entry level position in your company.

I interned at Infineon Technologies (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd. and was assigned to the Plant

Facilities Department. I was exposed to wastewater treatment processes and I believe my

internship experience and knowledge gained from my course will allow me to contribute to

your company.

I am looking for a position to kick-start my career as an engineer with the right amount of

exposure preferably in the field related to environmental engineering.

Lastly, I would like to express my sincere gratitude for the consideration and I would like the

chance to further elaborate my qualifications through an interview. My resume is attached

along with this cover letter. Looking forward to hearing from you.

Yours sincerely,

Subashini Venkatramanan

Cover Letter/ Subashini. V

1/3



Subashini Venkatramanan

Personal Particulars

Age : 24

Gender : Female

Identity Card No : 900103-01-6288

Email Address : supshi@hotmail.com

Phone number : 010-3705 742

Career Objective

To obtain an entry level position in order to further understand, apply and practice skills acquired at an undergraduate level in any relevant field applicable to environmental engineering principles.

Long Term Career Expectations

To specialize and lead in the field of consulting and/ or industry.

Education

Undergraduate : Bachelor of Engineering (Hons) Environmental Engineering

Institution : Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR)

Duration : May 2010 – May 2014

CGPA : 3.62

Achievements : First Class Honours, President's List (1 semester) and Dean's

List (5 semesters)

CV/ Subashini. V

Education (cont.)

Related Coursework : Environmental Impact Assessment

: Environmental Management System

: Wastewater Treatment: Solid Waste Management

: Environmental Health & Sanitation

: Renewable Energy

: Highway & Transportation System

High School : Malacca High School

Duration : June 2008 – December 2009

Qualification : STPM

CGPA : 2.67

Previous Work Experience

Company : Infineon Technologies (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd.

Position : Intern (Industrial Training) at Plant Facilities (PF) Department

Job Description : Waste water treatment plant (technology and legal requirements)

Duration : October 2012 – December 2012

Company : Raki Thomas & Ramanan, Charted Accountants

Position : Temporary

Job Description : Receptionist / Clerical assistant

Duration : March 2008 – May 2008

Skills and Strengths

Able to work in teams.

Computer Literacy : Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point, World Wide Web

Communication	Language	Spoken	Written	Presentation
[0=Poor, 10=Excellent]	English	10	8	8
	Malay	7	8	7

Compensation

Expected Salary : RM 2,600

CV/ Subashini. V